<people>
  <quincer>
    <name>Alexander	Jonkers</name>
    <email>alexander@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/alexanderjonkers?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=45968607&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Four years ago I started out as a young intern at Quince. I wasn’t really sure what I was getting myself into but four years later I’m still here as a member of the Quince design team. My work is quite diverse, from supporting the DTP department to building microsites.   
        Quince to me is a strong company because of the amount of care it has for its workers. We are a strong and social work force. 
        Keywords: crafts, gaming, photography]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Alexandru	Chiritescu</name>
    <email>alex@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Alexandru-Chiritescu.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=49427598&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[What I like and do most of the time is creating software by writing code. I enjoy experimenting and learning new things all the time, as a way of improving who I am and what I do.
        I'm a music addict, book reader and guitar playing novice. Curious by nature, I like socializing, exchanging ideas and straight answers. I believe that a warm and joyful attitude can make the world much better.
        Keywords: learn, play, improve]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>András Bálint Kisfaludy</name>
    <email>andras@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Andras_Balint.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Designer and excessive copy-paste abuser. Is a chill guy with a high level of attention to detail, who never rests in his leisure time - whether it's eSports or team sports (streetball), he pursues the game constantly to improve himself. Doesn't believe in personal intro texts.
        Keywords: design, detail, sports]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Andrea Bakos</name>
    <email>andi@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/andrea.t.bakos?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=54780659&locale=en_US&trk=tyah2]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[The great daydreamer, child of Gaia, music lover. She is an expert in travelling, addicted on outdoor programs and dogs. In front of the screen she spends most of her time filling rows and columns with financial data, beside that she tries to solve all Hungarian Quincers’ needs. If she loses her balance,  just let her run, or dance at a trance festival – these are her special ways to meditate. If you seek a mate for any kind of extreme sports she will be a good choice, but keep in mind: she is a solar depending entity!
        Keywords: sun, run, fun]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Anita Varga</name>
    <email>anita@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/juanitavarga]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=71237258&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Alias ’Metal Lady’ leads projects, aiming to deliver everything in Quince quality ánd meet deadlines. When the evening comes Metal Lady finds it relaxing to care for her flowers (she’s especially proud of her herb plants) and evoke travelling memories by cooking Mediterranean specialties while singing Italian oldies. We honestly recommend to taste her dishes, but avoid to listen to her aria.
Keywords: metal, flowers, travel]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Balázs Kovács</name>
    <email>balazs@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Balazs_Kovacs.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Loves to design, animate and solve problems. Used to play simulator games as a hobby, sometimes as a profession. His favourite form of transportation is the motorcycle.
        Keywords: design, simulators, motorcycle]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Bart van Asperen</name>
    <email>bart@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/rbvanasperen?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=65601029&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[My Quince shortlist consists of: design, production, 3D and learning all kinds of new stuff. The shortlist that typifies me personally includes (indoor) football, photography, reading, ex-Rotterdam, Feyenoord supporter and of course my wife Johanneke.
        Keywords: football, Rotterdam, design]]>
    </details>
    <section>Design / DTP</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Ben de Dood</name>
    <email>bendd@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/ben.dedood?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=10344291&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31641224756</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Loves to write or edit text - whatever it takes to create better copy -, loves to read and has a penchant for live concerts, tattoos and strange facts. His favorite form of transportation is the bicycle, but in his mind this lifelong Trekkie with a dark sense of humour travels at warp speed to explore the universe. 
        Keywords: rhetoric, books, outer space ]]>
    </details>
    <section>Copy</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Benjamin Weijers</name>
    <email>benjamin@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Benjamin_Weijers.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=100119952&locale=en_US&trk=tyah2]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Supporting, monitoring, testing all kinds of software related matters and improving workflow processes, that’s what gets Benjamin through the average Quince working day. Outside the office  this tall guy keeps the beaches and the waters  safe by acting as a lifeguard. He’s also a certified member of the Red Cross Events Team, so rest assured you can feel pretty safe with this guy around!
        Keywords: improvements, helping each other, lighten the burden]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Charles Meijboom</name>
    <email>charles@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/charles.meijboom?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=8861802&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[This Quincer knows how to develop a complete campaign in no time. Loves to create and have fun, at the office and at home. Family man. Proud father of two. Care taker. Thinking up practical solutions. Typical Amsterdam humour. Superb karaoke singer. Dedication. Big heart. Keywords: Ajax, responsible, jokes]]>
    </details>
    <section>Design / DTP</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Coen Schaafsma</name>
    <email>coen@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/coen.schaafsma?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=30840735&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Quince feels like a family business. That's why we work so well together. To make a long story short: pride, expertise, work hard, nice work, inspiration, respect, learn, friendship, openness, honesty, trust, pleasure, unity, family, a smile and a cold beer.
        Keywords: all of the above]]>
    </details>
    <section>Design / DTP</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Csaba Magyar</name>
    <email>csaba@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/magyarcs?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=45917945&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Knows the coding of love, the double-margin bug, static typing and action scripting, reads Bulgakov and can defend a 6 pool. At his screen you’ll see anything from structured queries to spreadsheets over eclipse tabs. As a music lover since the age of seven he listens to some random band from morning coffee until late in the evening while working, biking around or chilling in the city with friends.
        Keywords: Starcraft, coding, music]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Daniel Levitton</name>
    <email>daniel@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/levitton?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=55936184&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[By day an all-round designer @ Quince. By night a DJ and party organizer. 24 hours per day a sporty man who loves design and loves to create beautiful things.
        Key words: music, motorcycle, design, sport]]>
    </details>
    <section>Design / DTP</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>David Peperkamp</name>
    <email>david@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/david.peperkamp?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Quince is together and so am I. At the same time Quince is being yourself and so am I. To me it is also one big playground for creating beautiful things. To enter a room with a team and come out with something surprising. I love that. 
        My inspiration comes from the empty plan – when there’s nothing yet. My work includes campaigns, brand ID’s, retail activation, e-learning, displays and much more.
        Keywords: challenge, inspire, innovate]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Dávid Szakály</name>
    <email>david@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/davidope?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=48741576&authType=NAME_SEARCH&authToken=_jgu&locale=en_US&srchid=36dea3bf-7e06-468c-b728-5ee19b298029-0&srchindex=2&srchtotal=2&goback=%2Efps_PBCK_D%C3%A1vid+Szak%C3%A1ly_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*2_*1_Y_*1_*1_*1_false_1_R_*1_*51_*1_*51_true_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2&pvs=ps&trk=pp_profile_name_link]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>36205103372</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Faking concepts. Bending vectors. Spraying pixels. Commanding with scripts. Talking with gifs. Inhaling forest air, exhaling smoke. Stroking his self and a black dog called Jó. Kept alive by heavy basses, sugar and other stuff.
Keywords: all of the above and more]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Diederick	Koekkoek</name>
    <email>diederick@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/diederick.koekkoek?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[My typical day at Quince usually starts with … ‘mmm, wouldn’t it be great/smart/fun/epic if …’ then a lot of ‘tiktiktiktik… blablalabla… tiktik… &$@#*!... del del. Tik, blabla and hopefully Ahaaaa!’  
        Keywords: curiosity, anomalies, synergy, wonder]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Copy</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Djamel de Ligt</name>
    <email>djamel@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/djameldeligt?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=4610113&trk=nav_responsive_tab_profile_pic]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31624657437</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Globe trotter, single fin surfer, music lover and trends connoisseur. Operates in print media but is also known to develop or co-create just about everything from logos to websites and full-blown campaigns. If not at Quince, you can find him in the North Sea at Scheveningen, or in his beloved California, surfing the Great Ocean or hanging around on the beach.
        Keywords: surf dude, music, world]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Doruk Eker</name>
    <email>doruk@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/dorukeker?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=8730360&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31642378582</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I eat, drink, code, debug, research, try to inspire, be inspired, work out, chat and have fun…  and all that under the same roof. I am the non-Dutch Amsterdammer working happily at Quince. I develop interactive experiences for online, offline and mobile.
        Keywords: sports, music, art]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital / Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Eszter Holczingerné Tolnay-Knefély</name>
    <email>eszter@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/eszter.tolnayknefely?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Eszter is a true runner. In every sense of the word.  She doesn’t like public transport so she always runs to the office. And at the end of the day she runs back fast to her three children. For this proud mother Quince is her therapy. A place where she can ‘switch off’ the children for a while and “enjoy all the possibilities of working in the finance department, like invoicing, transferring and filling excels J”.
        Keywords: runner, mother, finance]]>
    </details>
    <section>Finance</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Eva Gransier</name>
    <email>eva@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/eva.gransier?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=32362420&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Always busy, love parties and make people happy. It made so much sense to incorporate that in my work! At Quince Events each day is different except for the colleagues who are invariably super nice and crazy, but in a good way. I really appreciate the opportunities for self-development and the amount of self-responsibility at Quince, must be one of the many reasons I still love my job!
        Keywords: shopping, organize, events]]>
    </details>
    <section>Event coördinator</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Ewout Thieme</name>
    <email>ewout@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/ewout.thieme?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=93738766&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Has joined the Quince development team working as a Java/Groovy/Grails developer, building web and Android applications but also handling IT tasks that require Unix/Linux knowledge, acting as a bridge between the boundaries of development and system administration. For his work he mostly uses Java based technology, but whenever he gets the chance he switches to the Ruby and Haskell programming languages. 
        Enjoys playing and experimenting with bleeding edge technology, playing computer games, snowboarding, watching movies and listening to music. 
        Keywords: technology, music, change]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Frans Deckers</name>
    <email>frans@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Frans_Deckers.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=44760311&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Graphic design, copy, user interface design, project management, storytelling, account management, coaching. Since I started at Quince in 2002, I’ve explored all my fields of interest. At Quince there are no limits in doing what you want to do. This made me into a creative with a unique set of skills. Just like my colleagues who feel like brothers and sisters to me. 
        With my fresh energy I’ll boost any campaign that is meant to cause a change; whether it is in the field of e-learning, branding or retail activation. Bang!
        Keywords: leadership, freshness, making a difference]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital Coördinator</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Frederik van Otterlo</name>
    <email>frederik@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Frederik_vOtterlo.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=22831013&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[One of the original metal heads in the studio. Creates still images and animates them on request. He’s into snowboarding, wakeboarding and scuba diving and is reputed to know a thing or two about Kung Fu, but he refuses to call any of these sports extreme. A silly joke is never lost on him. He much appreciates telling one himself or enjoying someone else’s sense of silly humor.
        Keywords: silly jokes, (frozen) water sports, metal music]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Gabor Foldvari</name>
    <email>gabor@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Gabor_Foldvari.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=75219640&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Living on the edge, Born to be Quincer, KPN for life
        Keywords: nature, traveling, expat community]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Gábor Bogosi</name>
    <email>gaborb@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/bogsa?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Loves to listen to and compose music, ride bikes (mountain bike and bmx), play and watch football (FC Barcelona), read (Asimov), take pictures, animate, amongst other things.
        Keywords: listen, play, read]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Gábor Varga</name>
    <email>gaborv@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/gaborv?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=45978128&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+36703257181</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Communicator, wine enthusiast, music lover and bit of a tech geek. At Quince, when he’s not dealing with clients, he’s out to meet new ones to co-create with. He enjoys riding his bike, having rosé spritzers with friends and, last but not least, the industry he works in. In a few years he hopes to brew his own social craft beer, and once ’old and wise’, do the same with wine.
Keywords: communicate, tech, the good things in life ]]>
    </details>
    <section>Client services / Business development</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>György Tolnay-Knefély</name>
    <email>gyuri@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/Gypapa?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=23895378&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Transparent and open minded. A dreamer, a leader, a thinker and a father who strives for better understanding of the world and it’s problem behind the problems to make a change. A change that connects people! Next to Quince, he can easily be found on random playgrounds of Budapest with his kids or on a bike somewhere downtown. If you call, he won’t answer... but he will call you back!
Keywords: lead, dream, think]]>
    </details>
    <section>Director Hungary</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Han Albers</name>
    <email>han@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/han.albers?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Rolling out projects, building exhibition stands for Events, that’s what I mostly do for Quince. This may have something to do with the fact that I’m a handy, practical kind of guy. When not working I like to play sports or just play. Whichever I fancy at the moment.
Keywords: work hard play hard]]>
    </details>
    <section>Events</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>István Tütto</name>
    <email>istvan@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/istvantutto?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Is always very curious. He likes to discover whatever interesting there is to find in technology and art. He spends countless hours together with his colleagues to provide a higher standard quality of graphic 
design. Also he has a passion to create things that react and adapt to changes in their environment. He hasn’t built his first robot yet, but he surely strides in that direction.
Keywords: graphic design, technology, react & adapt]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Jamel van Laarhoven</name>
    <email>jamel@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jamel.vanlaarhoven?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=126038616&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[At Quince Events I manage projects from A to Z. I love to add details for the final  touch, am quite used to working in the weekends (comes with the job) and would rather skip the mornings if possible (which is not the case). In my spare time I like to kitesurf in the summer or snowboard in the winter. Work hard, play hard. That’s what they say, right?
        Keywords: hotel lobbies, cocktails, audio visual products]]>
    </details>
    <section>Event coördinator</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>James Guy</name>
    <email>james@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>no</useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/James_Guy.jpg</image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/james.guy.967?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=6695332&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31629497283</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Passionate account manager who during week days is inspired by his colleagues and clients to create solutions for goals which are yet undefined … So James’ maxim “Doing the impossible by doing it” is not that surprising. Neither that Mandela is his inspiration. On Saturdays he devotes his free time as a soccer team manager who guides young talented football players through the adventure called professional soccer. What does it mean to be a professional player? And what hurdles do these youngsters need to take? There is no easy route.
        “If I can reach one out of twenty, my goal has been fulfilled”
        Key words: Mandela, travelling, reading, movies]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Jeffrey Kors</name>
    <email>jeffreyk@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jeffrey.kors.3?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I’m Jeffrey, intern at the Events team. I am learning a lot at Quince! My colleagues really involve me in everything and I’ve got acquainted with several parts of the Events business already. I help out building exhibition stands and have made a lot of great rides with the crew. I even baked pan cakes at an event. Also I’ve met a whole bunch of new, really nice people!
        Keywords: soccer, Telstar, drinking beer with friends]]>
    </details>
    <section>Handy man</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Jeffrey Schulz</name>
    <email>jeffrey@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jeffrey.schulz.7?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[This well-organised and deadline driven Quincer loves to create for the creatives. With a smile on his face he juggles through the day to get every job done. And he’s doing so successfully. So there must be some truth in Jeffrey’s comparison: “Traffic is like juggling, making sure no ball will drop.”  J
        Key words: daughter, deadline, traffic]]>
    </details>
    <section>Traffic</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Jeroen van Delft</name>
    <email>jeroen@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jeroenvandelft?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=25128808&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Transforming functional wishes of clients into working solutions, that’s the daily challenge for this long-time developer. He also programs stuff in his spare time, which resulted for instance in a neat film planner to accommodate a hobby he shares with several friends. One day he would really love to see the introduction of an actual Star Trek style replicator. Still being the practical guy: “This will solve a lot of problems ánd save a lot of time.”
        Keywords: movies, technology, solutions]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>

  <quincer>
    <name>Jeroen van der Horst</name>
    <email>jeroenh@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jeroen.vanderhorst.90?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=36825708&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31615642775</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Hi! Because of my love and fascination for photography and film, I have founded Quince DOK, the photography and video subsidiary of Quince Amsterdam. We add more value to the retail and marketing solutions that Quince is known for. By deploying innovative techniques, different tools and a wide range of technical and creative experts we make even the craziest visual ideas reality.
        Keywords: Quince DOK, photography, film]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Jessica Dekker</name>
    <email>jessica@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/jessica.dekker.39?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=152502742&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[During workdays dancing Queen Jessica is responsible for several accounts. And she always delivers her absolute best. In her spare time she loves to travel, have fun with friends and family, work out and of course dance, dance, dance. Preferably all night long. Key words: accurate, creativity, dedication]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Joyce de Groot</name>
    <email>joyce@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Joyce_dGroot.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=88668206&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Good afternoon, this is Quince, Joyce speaking! How can I help you? This sporty-spice, multitasking Quince lady helps out on whatever job you have for her. And always with a happy face. In her free time she gets her kicks out of running, winter sports, salsa and exploring Amsterdam where she recently found a nice crib.
        Key words: festivals, spider in the web, organising]]>
    </details>
    <section>Office</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Julian Gallimore</name>
    <email>julian@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/julian.gallimore.5?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=73022006&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I cannot tell you where I'm from, because I grew up a bit everywhere. What I can tell you is that I'm enthusiastic and passionate about new techniques and developments in programming. Here at Quince, I work a lot on interactive displays, developing our backend system that manages our interactive applications. I also do some front end development, creating mobile friendly web applications. Outside of work, my curiosity takes me to countries I haven't seen yet. Besides that, I love watching movies and playing games, and on those few sunny days that we get here, nothing can stop me from being outdoors.
        Key words: Development, games, outdoors]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital / Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>László Nyúzó</name>
    <email>laszlo@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/laszlo.nyuzo?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[The ‘biggest’ PHP developer at Quince Budapest. Amateur boxer and musician, plays bass guitar and drums in jazz, funky and rock bands. Always crooning and singing, using the furniture as his personal drum sets. Though he is the biggest, he is also  one of the youngest of the team. In his free time, he enjoys being near water. River, lake, or ocean, you name it!
        Keywords: boxing, music, water]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Linda Lodewijk</name>
    <email>linda@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/linda.lodewijk.7?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=102394608&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[This Quince lady is good with words. She loves to write all sorts of copy, from ad campaigns and corporate texts to scripts and voice overs. Has a thing for vampires and Dutch sayings since childhood. Huge soft spot for ginger tomcats. Loves to be at the water(side) and watch movies. A city girl that finds rest in nature and being with loved ones. Playful and persistent nature. Curious, committed, old school rap.]]>
    </details>
    <section>Copy</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Lisette Koot</name>
    <email>lisette@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/lkoot?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=72345720&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Money, money, money …
        My work at Quince involves a lot of numbers and bills. And although my job description isn’t well known by my colleagues, they do like it a lot when their salary gets paid in time.
        I’m a real outdoor kind of Quincer enjoying (in no particular order) food, music, fun with friends, festivals, travelling, sporting … just doing something!!!
        Reading good books relaxes me.
        Key words: fun, finance, family]]>
    </details>
    <section>Finance</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Lotte de Jong</name>
    <email>lotte@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Lotte_dJong.jpg</image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/lotte.dejong.71?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=133013657&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Working at Events is challenging to this born and raised Egmond beach babe, who nowadays enjoys living close to Beach South (Strand Zuid) in Amsterdam. “Each day is full of surprises, you never know what to expect. I make a lot of fun with my crazy colleagues and learn new things every single day … on the most various subjects.” J
        Key words: cooking, festivals, friends]]>
    </details>
    <section>Event coördinator</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Marcel Kors</name>
    <email>marcel@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/marcel.kors.3?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Everything is related to a number, I am born with numbers, I work with numbers and I’ll end up as a number, somewhere in time… I collect the money, I pay the bills bills bills. That’s what I basically do at Quince. But make no mistake: I love my job and all my colleagues, my motorbike (a BMW R1200GSA), running, the sun and last but certainly not least my kids Jeffrey and Mitchel.
        Keywords: numbers, numbers, numbers]]>
    </details>
    <section>Finance</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Marco Comparato</name>
    <email>marco@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/marco.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=96222067&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Marco concepts, designs, and creates advanced interactive solutions, and is an evangelist for creative-technologies through Adobe, Google, and Open-Source tool-sets.  He is an American ex-pat from SF/LA/NYC.
        ]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Marijn Bouma</name>
    <email>marijn@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/marijnbouma?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=6998970&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Quincer since 2001. Front-End. Java. Security. Performance. Groovy. Grails. Research. Android. On a continuing journey to discover the world through travel, eating, cooking and music.
        Keywords: develop, discover, world.]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Mark Rondema</name>
    <email>mark@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/mark.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=29007584&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I'm the guy who fixes things. I'm the guy who makes magic from al kind of materials. But most of all I'm the guy who always keeps smiling :-) 
        Keywords: shooting pool, sailing, devising technical solutions]]>
    </details>
    <section>Traffic</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Martijn Bon</name>
    <email>martijnb@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Martijn_Bon.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[All-round happy worker. Always-studying-linguistic-healthy-eating-festival-tiger.
        Keywords: 3D, print, digital, interaction design]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Martijn Thieme</name>
    <email>martijn@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/martijnt?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=2777140&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details></details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Miranda Kasius</name>
    <email>miranda@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/mirandakasius?fref=ts&ref=br_tf]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=224798130&locale=nl_NL&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[My work at Quince? I can handle 56 countries… and still counting. Being the peanutbutter between the sandwich of our designers & developers and all these foreign countries makes me feel on top of the world! Inside and outside of the office I am a happy girl who loves to enjoy life! I like to spend my spare time being creative; cook & bake, play with make-up, make handmade stamps, create lampshades, face/bodypainting. You can make me happy with a themed dress-up party and a great glass of wine served with some nice food!
        Keywords: happy, positive, YOLO!]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Olaf Weijers</name>
    <email>olaf@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Olaf_Weijers.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Of my activities, which encompass executing all email communications for our clients within Quince, I like testing the best. Just breaking sites and tools apart and going over every option in detail.
        Keywords: games (rpg’s), Japan, friends]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Patrick Weijers</name>
    <email>patrick@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Patrick_Weijers.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details></details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Ralf Amama</name>
    <email>ralf@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/ralf.martin.amama?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=182627132&locale=nl_NL&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[At Quince I’m a Jack of all trades. Helping out Events, taking care of office maintenance, stuff like that. Since my roots are from the creative side, I can also help out in the digital department.
        I’m what you call a textbook geek. I like Star Wars, games, movies, comics, you name it! I also like ancient cultures and travelling, the more when these go together.
        Keywords: geek culture, Ford Mustang, travel]]>
    </details>
    <section>Handy man</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Raymond Schoos</name>
    <email>raymond@quinceretailsolutions.com</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/raymond.schoos?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
<![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=127912798&authType=NAME_SEARCH&authToken=Hifi&locale=en_US&srchid=14e0a509-6b76-4faa-bd60-2dd769173288-0&srchindex=1&srchtotal=2&goback=%2Efps_PBCK_raymond+schoos_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*2_*1_Y_*1_*1_*1_false_1_R_*1_*51_*1_*51_true_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2&pvs=ps&trk=pp_profile_name_link]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Technology, it’s all around me! Hi I’m Raymond, working for Quince Retail Solutions. I’m there to provide you the best customer experience possible!
        Keywords: gadgets, freedom, website creation, new born baby, creativity]]>
    </details>
    <section>Quince Retail Solutions</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Remco Schoos</name>
    <email>remco@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Remco_Schoos.jpg</image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/schoos?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=9568252&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Entrepreneur. Creating tangible things from abstract ideas. Gadget freak, technology enabled solutions. Making things practical. Playful. Making cool stuff work in retail. Enjoying the Quince team and colleagues. Proud to be Quince. Happy with the dedication of our colleagues. New stuff and new ideas are always popping in my head, always busy writing ideas down to use them whenever and wherever possible.
 Keywords: All of the above]]>
    </details>
    <section>Quince Retail Solutions</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Rene van Bakel</name>
    <email>rene@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/rene.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=49775719&authType=NAME_SEARCH&authToken=RUAz&locale=en_US&srchid=7cc58d81-bffd-49eb-a901-cc28fa5aa040-0&srchindex=1&srchtotal=14&goback=%2Efps_PBCK_rene+van+bakel_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*1_*2_*1_Y_*1_*1_*1_false_1_R_*1_*51_*1_*51_true_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2_*2&pvs=ps&trk=pp_profile_name_link]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I’m a web developer. In addition I often give advice in other project about possible solutions and I lead a number of projects. Colleagues tell me they think I am ‘sweet’ and ‘caring’. That must be the reason I don’t shy from household chores, not even at Quince. My inspiration comes from my wife Amanda and my daughter Andrea, my natural curiosity about how things/people/animals work and from people who do what feels good, no matter what other people think.
        Keywords: family, care, curiosity]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Richárd Kovács</name>
    <email>richard@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/richard.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=140040997&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Richmond: racing maniac, traveling through time and space at warp speed on the waves of spirituality surrounded by rainbow colored bytecodes. Don't be late when you bring him his Friday pizza.
        Keywords: racing, traveling, bytecodes]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Robin Kooiker</name>
    <email>robin@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/robin.kooiker.5?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[My work at Quince includes devising and designing new campaigns and designing all kinds of things in 2D and 3D, ranging from touchdisplays to artwork. I like it so much, even in my spare time I design stuff. What inspires me is also about design, namely interior design and furniture design. But of course there’s more that’s important to me: Marieke, Daan and Melle, Ajax, watching movies at home, cooking. Quince has made me who I am as a designer and a person. Yes, the Quince shape is pretty much there (literal and figurativeJ).
        Keywords: design, family, Quince]]>
    </details>
    <section>Design / DTP</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Ryan van Esch</name>
    <email>ryan@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/ryan.vanesch.7?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=131375029&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I’m versatile on every project big or small, from A to Z. Working in the inspiring Quince events team is like being busy with a hobby, which gives me a tremendous amount of positive energy. I have an eye for detail. Do it right or don’t do it all. And in the meantime enjoy life! J
        Keywords: teamwork, versatile, open minded, sport]]>
    </details>
    <section>Events</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Sander Sneek</name>
    <email>sanders@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/sander.sneek?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=13297711&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I am an interactive developer who likes to tinker with new technologies / gadgets while listening to the best band ever: Underworld. Blowing off some steam with making music, wakeboarding, running and spending quality time with the fam :-).
        Keywords: King Of Snake, family, technology, music]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital / Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Sander Scherphuis</name>
    <email>sander@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Sander_Scherphuis.jpg</image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/sander.scherphuis?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=60631940&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Leader of the Quince pack. Passionate motivator. Event master. Entrepreneur with heart and soul. Proud dad. Someone you can count on. Always aims for the highest score in work and life. Creating impressive concepts and campaigns together makes him happy. Never gives up anddoesn’t believe in ‘cannot’. Always respectful and truly playful. Loves to relax on the water. Key words: never stop learning]]>
    </details>
    <section>Director</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Sjoerd Liefting</name>
    <email>sjoerd@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/sjoerd.liefting?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/pub/sjoerd-liefting/5/73a/865]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[A good visual tells me more than a thousand words. I love new, cool concepts, clean designs and open minded clients. When not at work I like to travel and see new places, bike around in the city, hang out on the beach, listen to new music, challenge myself in sports, have a good talk and laugh with friends and play with my always enthusiastic kids. Keywords: visual, new, play]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Solko Detmers</name>
    <email>solko@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/legologic?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=12041634&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31612595906</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Doing IT at Quince has been truly challenging over the last couple of years and has taught me to think outside of the box. My work is best described as helping out with all the technicalities in the background, thus enabling part of the creative processes within Quince and showcasing them to the world. My IT philosophy starts with enabling people to work in a pleasant working environment. it starts with people’s needs and is supported with technical solutions… in that order!
        Keywords: respect all living things, capture beauty or oddness using photography, personal growth]]>
    </details>
    <section>Datacenter / ICT</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Tamás Zsolt Damu</name>
    <email>zsolt@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/zsolt.t.damu?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Hi my name is Zsolt but my friends call me Caesar. I’m a Java developer with a preference for developing the back-end. In my leisure time I really like (to play) sports with a ball except for the ones that require a swimming pool, certain online multiplayer games, and spend time with friends. I also have a liking for non-figurative tattoos, especially the ones on my own body;-)
Keywords: Java, ball sports, tattoos]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Theodoros	Papadopoulos</name>
    <email>theodoros@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Theodoros_Papadopoulos.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin></linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[This Greek guy is part of the Quince development team, participating in the technical design and implementation of various software projects. Loves doing the ‘non common - non trivial’, both in work and in life, when possible. Deep interest in history, philosophy, human development, engineering sciences and spiritual traditions globally.
        Keywords: Know-the-natural-order]]>
    </details>
    <section>Development</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Tímea	Mónus</name>
    <email>timi@quince.hu</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Timea_Monus.jpg</image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/timea.monus?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=132687893&locale=en_US&trk=tyah2]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[As a member of the design crew she spends her time designing trainings and any other fancy stuff in and out of the office. Furthermore she loves travelling the world, the sights, old buildings in beautiful cities or the countryside and sketching down or taking photos of anything that grabs her imagination. Whether on horseback or on a bike, she's always on the go, preferably with friends. Listening to music and dancing are her favorite ways to relax, but on a hot summer day her attraction to colorful cones of ice cream may takes over.
        Keywords: travel, transport, ice cream]]>
    </details>
    <section>Concept / Design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Tjeerd van der Hulst</name>
    <email>tjeerd@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Tjeerd_vdHulst.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=15562487&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Tjeerd is me. I love to play the guitar, draw funny stuff, cook, read, and after a few beers you might catch me trying to drive people crazy by doing card tricks. Nature never ceases to amaze me. I have a strong interest in the human mind and all its mysteries and love to ponder the ineffable. 
        At Quince I play around with all kinds of digital design and animation. In the meantime I’m actually an undercover field researcher of abnormal groups of crazy people in their own habitat.
        Keywords: music, nature, imagination]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Tulay Kocaoglu</name>
    <email>tulay@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/tulay.amama?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=211547840&locale=nl_NL&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Hey! I am Tulay, digital designer. I design websites, e-mail templates, banners and so on. Recently I’ve started learning how to make videos in AfterEffects. I’m doing pretty well and enjoying it a lot. Animating is so much fun! Especially when you have created something yourself that comes alive. 
        Gaming is a great hobby of mine, both on pc or console. I am also a passionate Star Wars and kimono collector. Finally, I am a very creative kind of girl and in a good mood every single day.
        Keywords: cats, kimonos, games]]>
    </details>
    <section>Digital design</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Vincent van der Laan</name>
    <email>vincent@quinceretailsolutions.com</email>
    <useFBImage></useFBImage>
    <image>assets/img/profiles/Vincent_vd_Laan.jpg</image>
    <facebook></facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=5390579&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile>+31657934433</mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[I love translating issues into goals and actions; bringing together online and offline strategy managed from one central system.
        Keywords: people, cooking, new technology]]>
    </details>
    <section>Quince Retail Solutions</section>
  </quincer>
  <quincer>
    <name>Wout Niebuur</name>
    <email>wout@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/wout.niebuur?fref=ts]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=35419618&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Work hard to play hard. Some people call me a deadline junky. I just like to make the impossible possible:-)
        Keywords: work, play, work, play]]>
    </details>
    <section>Events</section>
  </quincer>
  
  <quincer>
    <name>Wouter Koot</name>
    <email>wouter@quince.nl</email>
    <useFBImage>yes</useFBImage>
    <image></image>
    <facebook>
      <![CDATA[https://www.facebook.com/wouter.koot.3]]>
    </facebook>
    <linkedin>
      <![CDATA[http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=96222067&locale=en_US&trk=tyah]]>
    </linkedin>
    <mobile></mobile>
    <details>
      <![CDATA[Nice to meet you! I’m a proud member of the sales staff of Quince Retail Solutions. Have you seen our beautiful showroom yet? I love my work and making clients happy makes me happy. You can say I’m a real ‘sports guy’. Doing sports relaxes me and re-energies my battery, so I can get the best out of every day and the next.
To me a solid foundation is essential for personal development and growth. Keywords:  accurate, winter sports, friends]]>
    </details>
    <section>Project leader</section>
  </quincer>
  
</people>
